Benjamin Vaughan Papers 1746-1900 Mss.B.V46p
American Philosophical Society
- Series II. General Correspondence, 1746-1952; 6.5 linear feet (Box 2-27)
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 November [December] 6; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - AL to Captain Carr, 1799 December 11; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 December 11; 3 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 December 14; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 December 14; 3 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, 1762-1827
  - AL to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, [1799 December 14]; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - AL to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 December 15; 3 p.; Collins, John
  - ALS to [Cavendish, Henry, 1731-1810 ?], 1799 December 20; 11 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 December 29; 2 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 December 31; 3 p.; Collins, John, Jr.
  - Als to the editor of the Kennebec Intelligence, 1799 December; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - MS, Character and Life of Washington selected with a few alterations from the book of Ecclesiasticies, [ ca. 1799]; 3 p.
  - ALS to [Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835], [1799?]; 1 p.; Collins, John, Jr.
  - MS, papers pertaining to the use of timber to build vessels, 1799-1820; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
    Contains accounts and memorandums.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, [1799?]; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, [1799?]; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, [1799?]; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, [1799?]; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 January 11; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Landsdowne, William Petty, Marquis of, 1737-18o5, 1800 January 25; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 January 29; 3 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 January 29; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 January 30; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 February 14; 2 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 February 19, March 18; 3 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 February 24; 6 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839, 1800 March 15; 2 p.; Merrick, John, 1766-1861; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Mrs. Charles, 1800 March 17; 2 p.; Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 March 17; 6 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 March 18; 15 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 March 29; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 April 16; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Samuel, 1720-1802 and Son, 1800 April 17, May 17; 4 p.; Spooner, Andrew,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 April 18; 4 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 April 18; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - AL to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 April 19; 3 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 April 20; 6 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 May 7; 2 p.; Heywood and Thompson
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 May 10; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - AL to Judge Robbins, 1800 May 12; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to [Jenner, Edward, 1749-1823], 1800 May 15; 2 p.; Cline, Henry
  - ALS to Vaughan, William, 1752-1850, 1800 May 15; 1 p.; Jenner, Edward, 1749-1823
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 May 16; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 May 20; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 May 26; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 May 26; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 May 27; 2 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 May 27; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 May 29; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 June 9; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - AL to Vaughan, Samuel, 1720-1802 and son, 1800 June 10; p. 1; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - Als to Vaughan, Samuel, 1762-, 1800 June 14; 8 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Howard, Col., Dearborn, Gen., and Hallowell, Robert, 1800 June 17; 4 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
    includes copy.
  - AL to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 June 17; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 June 17; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 June 19; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 June 20; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 June 28; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 July 3; 2 p.; Stone, J. W
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 October 29; 2 p.; Stone, J. W
    Housed with former letter.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 July 6; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 July 8; 5 p.; Collins, John
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 July 8; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 July 13; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 July 15; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 July 15; 2 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 July 17; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 July 18; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 July 19; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 July 19; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 July 22; 1 p.; Heywood & Thompson
  - AMS, description of Winthrop, Maine, 1800 July 21; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
    - Draft of the town of Winthrop, Maine, 1797 May 19; 1 map, 32.7 x 24.8 cm; Jones, John
      Colored.
      Other Finding Aids note
      Realms of Gold, 51 (1).
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 July 24; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 July 24; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, [1800 July?]; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 August 10; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 August 11; 3 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1851-1835, 1800 August 13; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1851-1835, 1800 August 16; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1851-1835, 1800 August 24; 4 p.; Spooner, Andrew,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1851-1835 and Merrick, John, 1766-1861, 1800 August 26; 4 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802
  - ALS to [Vaughan, Benjamin, 1851-1835], 1800 August 26; 3 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to [Vaughan, Benjamin, 1851-1835], 1800? August; 1 p.; Prescott, Benjamin
  - AMS. Power of attorney to Messrs. Howard, Henry Dearborn and Robert Hallowell, 1800 September 1; 1 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 September 4; 4 p.; Nichols, F
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 September 5; 10 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 September 6; 3 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - AMS, Deed of lands to Rebecca Merrick or to Benjamin Vaughan for exchange of lands, 1800 September 6; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Mrs. Livingston, 1800 September 16; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 September 17; 3 p.; Desbassayns, Henry
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 September 23; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 September 23; 1 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 September 25; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 September 25; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS, 1800 September 27; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 September 27; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Vaughan, Samuel, 1762-, 1800 September 30; 4 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 October 4; 2 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - AL to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835 and Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1800 October 7, December 8; 4 p.; Lansdowne, William Petty, Marquis of, 1737-1805
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 October 8; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 October 14; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 October 14; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 October 16; 9 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
    Includes two copies.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 October 16; 3 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 October 16; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 October 24; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 October 25; 1 p.; Manning, Anderson, and Bosanquet.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 October 27; 2 p.; Desbassayns, Henry
    In french.
  - ALS to Weston, Samuel, 1800 October 31; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 November 18; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Samuel, 1720-1802 and son, 1800 November 19; 9 p.; Carto, M
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 November 30; 1 p.; Hallowell, Robert,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 December 1; 4 p.; Russell, William, 1740-1818
  - ALS to Vaughan, Samuel 1720-1802 and son, 1800 December 10; 2 p.; Spooner, Andrew,
  - DS, Minutes, 1800 December 11; 1 p.; Kennebec, Maine. Agricultural Society.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 December 14; 2 p.; Desbassayns, Henry
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 December 19; 1 p.; Spooner, Andrew,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 December 26; 6 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 December 26; 6 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 December 29; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to [Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835], 1800 December 30; 4 p.; Eustis, William
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1800 December 31; 1 p.; Nichols, F
  - AMs, State of Facts as to American Lands, [ca. 1800?]; 3 p.
    concerning certain lands in Maine.
  - AMs, Account of Calvin's treatment of servetus, [ca. 1800?]; 13 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, [1800?]; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835 and Merrick, John, 1766-1861, 1801 January 5; 3 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
    Regarding family estate.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 January 5; 13 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835 and Merrick, John, 1766-1861, 1801 January 6; 3 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - AL to [Dexter, Aaron?], 1801 January 7; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 January 14; 3 p.; Wells, William,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 January 21; 3 p.; Le Favre, Nicholas
  - AL to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 January 21; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 January 21; 4 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - AL to Rush, Benjamin, 1746-1813, 1801 January 24; 59 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 January 25; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 January 29; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 January 30; 2 p.; Sigoumey and sons
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 January 31; 3 p.; Jefferies, Edward,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 February 9; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - AMs, concerning Hannah Reading, 1801 February 10; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 February 12; 3 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ADS, Articles of agreement with Nicholas Le Favre, 1801 February 12; 18 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ADS, receipt of books from Benjamin Vaughan, 1801 February 13; 1 p.; Johnston, David
  - ADS, Memorandum concerning an agreement with Nicholas Le Favre pertaining to steam engines, 1801 February 13. March 21; 26 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - Al to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 February 20; 3 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - AlS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 February 21; 4 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - AlS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 February 25; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - Al to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, [1801] February 27; 4 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 February; 4 p.; Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 March 2; 2 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 March 5; 2 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 March 5; 3 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 March 6; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 March 10; 2 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802
    includes copy
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835 and Merrick, John, 1766-1861, 1801 March 10; 1 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 March 10; 1 p.; Vaughan, Sarah; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 March 14; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS, 1801 March 16; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS, 1801 March 19; 2 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 March 20; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
    housed with previous letter.
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 March 21; 4 p.; Dearborn, Henry, 1751-1829
  - ALS to Dickason, Thomas and Amory, R. G, 1801 March 21; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 March 31; 1 p.; Jefferson, Thomas.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 March 31; 3 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 April 9; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 April 10; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 April 14; 2 p.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 April 22; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 April 26; 3 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 May 3; 2 p.; Russell, William, 1740-1818
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1801 May 11; 3 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 May 18; 1 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 May 18; 3 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to [Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835], 1801 May 19; 3 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 May 20; 8 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 May 23; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ADS, Definition of property tranferred by Charles Vaughan to B. Prescott, 1801 May 29; 1 p.; Small, H
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 June 5; 4 p.; Dearborn, Henry, 1751-1829
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 June 5; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 June 7; 2 p.; Jefferson, Thomas, 1743-1826
  - AL to [Lansdowne, William Petty, Marquis of, 1737-1805], 1801 June 8; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 June 8; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
    Regarding the Hallowell family property.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 June 11; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Hallowell, Robert, 1801 June 12; 1 p.; Johnston, David; Stewart, Robert
  - ALS to Hallowell, Robert, 1801 June 14; 3 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
    Legal matters regarding the Hallowell family estate.
  - ALS to [Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835], 1801 June 16; 2 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ADS, Invoice of items shipped to Benjamin Vaughan, 1801 June 19; 1 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835 and Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1801 June 28, 29; 3 p.; Vaughan, Henry
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 June 29; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 July 2; 3 p.; Wells, William,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 July 8; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 July 12; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 July 12; 5 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
    Regarding Family estate.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 July 14; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 August 1; 1 p.; Parker, Daniel
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 August 3; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
    Regarding the Hallowell estate.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 August 4; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 August 5; 4 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 August 6; 3 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 August 26; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 August 27; 3 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to [Merrick, John, 1766-1861], [1801 September 1]; 3 p.; Vaughan, Henry
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1801 September 2; 2 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - AL to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 September 3; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 September 5; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 September 12; 4 p.; Rush, Benjamin, 1746-1813
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 September 12; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ADS, Enumeration of the inhabitants of the District of Maine to Benjamin Vaughan, 1801 October 12; 21 p.; Parker, Isaac, 1768-1830
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1801 October 14; 3 p.; Mme Foache and Mn L'abbe Hatry
    Partially in French.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 October 14; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 October 26; 2 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 October 27; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Parker, Isaac, 1768-1830, 1801 October 29; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 November 2; 1 p.; Dexter, Aaron
  - AL to [Dexter, A], 1801 November 12; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
    Housed with previous letter.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 November 3; 1 p.; Hallowell, Robert,
  - AL to Vaughan, Samuel, 1720-1802 and Son, 1801 November 5; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Dear Uncle, 1801 November 7; 13 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 November 10; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 November 10; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, John, 1756-1841, 1801 November 6; 1 p.; Amory, R. G
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 December 3; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Samuel, 1720-1802 and son, 1801 December 9; 2 p.; Bernard, David
  - ALS to Bernard, David, 1802 February 8; 2 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1801 December 23; 3 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - AL to Vaughan, Samuel, 1762-, 1801 December 28; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - AL to Vaughan, Samuel, 1762-, 1801 December 21; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to [Vaughan, Samuel, 1720-1802 and Son?], 1801 December 30, 31; 2 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, 1762-1827
  - ALS to Lowell, John, Jr, 1801 December 31; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839, [1801]; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AMs, Concerning land speculation in Kennebec, [ca. 1801?]; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AMs, Concerning the failure of Andrew Spooner and Charles Vaughan, [ca. 1801]; 12 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AD, Notes on the census, [18001?]; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - Ads, List of Books forwarded to Benjamin Vaughan, [ca. 1801]; 3 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan William, 1752-1850, 1802 January 7; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Parker, Daniel, 1802 January 7; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
    Written on the back of previous letter.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839 and Spooner, A, 1802 January 8; 6 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802
  - AL to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1802 January 12; 3 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
    Regarding bills.
    torn. Part of the letter is missing.
  - AL to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1802 January 12; 8 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
    Regarding family accounts and estate.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1802 January 21; 3 p.; Dutton, Samuel
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1802 January 28; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1802 February 5; 3 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - AL to [Vaughan, Samuel, 1720-1802 and son], 1798 January 12; 1 p.; Bernard, David
  - AL to [Vaughan, Samuel, 1720-1802 and son], 1798 April 19; 2 p.; Bernard, David
  - AL to Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839, 7 February 1798; 1 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802
    Extract of letter.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Samuel, 1720-1802 and son, 30 April 1798; 1 p.; Bernard, David
  - ALS to Bernard, David, 8 Febraury 1802; 2 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802
  - AL to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, [1802] February 10; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1802 February 12; 2 p.; Boylston, Ward Nicholas
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1802 February 12; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1802 February 17; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1802 February 18; 2 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to [Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835], 1802 February 18; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
    Letter torn.
  - ALS ro Bernard, David, 1802 February 20; 2 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802
  - ALS to [Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835], 1802 February 23; 2 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802
    Regarding Henry Vaughan.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, [1804 February 24]; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Bernard, David, 1802 February 25; 2 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1802 February 25; 3 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850